Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Faculty Publications, 1844-1994 RG.1.1
New York University Archives
- Faculty Publications, 21411
  - Coates, C.W., Cox, R.T., Rosenblith, W.A., Brown, M. Vertner; Propagation of the Electric Impulse Along the Organs of the Electric Eel, 1940; 21585 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Burton, Milton, Davis, Thomas W., Gordon, Alvin, Taylor, H. Austin; The Photolysis of Ketene and the Structure of Methylene, 1956; 21584 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Davis, Thomas W., Burton, Milton; The Potential Energy Relationships in Normal and Excited Acetaldehyde, 1939; 21583 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Lucas, Henry C., Jr.; The Analysis, Design, and Implementation of Information Systems, 1976; 21582 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227013 5
  - Lounsbury, Ralph Greenlee; The British Fishery at Newfoundland, 1634-1763, 1934; 21581 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Park, Joseph H.; The English Reform Bill of 1867 (2 copies), 1920; 21580 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Park, Joseph H.; The English Working Men and the American Civil War (2 copies), 1924; 21579 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Lounsbury, Ralph Greenlee; Yankee Trade at Newfoundland (from the New England Quarterly), 1930; 21578 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Parker, Richard; Some Additional Sources of Dumas' Les Trois Musketeres (from Modern Philology), 1944; 21577 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Landgraf, John L.; Land Use in the Ramah Area of New Mexico: An Anthropological Approach to the Aerial Study, 1954; 21576 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Heaton, Harry Clifton; Another Pieza de Titulos de Comedias, 1929; 21575 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Heaton, Harry Clifton; Lope de Vega's Part 27 Extravagant, 1924; 21574 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Draper, John William; Scientific Memoirs, Being Experimental Contributions to a Knowledge of Radiant Energy, 1878; 21573 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fryer, Douglas; The Measurement of Interests, 1931; 21572 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Gillett, E.H.; The Moral System, with an Historical and Critical Introduction, 1874; 21571 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Proceedings of the Meeting of the Officers of the Colleges and Academies, with address by Taylor Lewis on Liberal Education, 1863; 21570 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Palmer, Richard, and Otto, Christian F.; Weissenhoff 1927 and the Modern Movement in Architecture, 1991; 21569 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Park, Joseph Hendershot; British Prime Ministers of the Nineteenth Century: Policies and Speeches (2 copies), 1950; 21568 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Pollock, Thomas Clark; The Nature of Literature: Its Relation to Science, Religion, and Human Experience, 1942; 21567 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Pike, James S.; The Prostrate State: South Carolina Under Negro Government, 1935; 21566 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Knowlton, Daniel C., and Tilton, J. Warren; Motion Pictures in History Teaching, 1929; 21565 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Brill, Jeanette G., and Payne, E. George; The Adolescent Court and Crime Prevention, 1938; 21564 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Prokosch, E.; The Sounds and History of the German Language, 1916; 21563 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Paine, Martyn; A Discourse on the Soul and Instinct, 1849; 21562 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Labberton and Marks; The Marine Engineer's Handbook, 1945; 21561 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - MacCracken, Henry Noble; The Family on Gramercy Park (2 copies), 1949; 21560 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227014 3
  - Radossawljewitsch, Paul R.; Das Fortschreiten des Vergessens mit der Zeit, undated; 21559 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Magee, James Dysart; Materials for the Study of Banking, 1923; 21558 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - MacCracken, John Henry; College and Commonwealth, 1920; 21557 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell; The Three Essentials (2 copies), 1901; 21556 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell; Andrew Haswell Green: A Memorial Address, 1903; 21555 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Henry Mitchell MacCracken: In Memoriam (2 copies), 1923; 21554 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Magoffin, R.V.D. and Davis, Emily C.; Magic Spades: The Romance of Archaeology, 1929; 21553 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Kimball, Fiske; American Architecture, 1928; 21552 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Granniss, Ruth Shepard; The Work of a Book Club, 1937; 21551 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous publications in chemistry by Arthur E. Hill, 1923-1931; 21550 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Richards, Theodore W., ed.; The Scientific Work of Morris Loeb, 1913; 21549 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell; The Hall of Fame, 1901; 21548 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Magoffin, Ralph VanDeman; The Lure and Lore of Archaeology, 1930; 21547 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - MacDougall, Robert; The General Problems of Psychology Conceptions, 1922; 21546 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Reed, Anna Y.; Occupational Placement, 1946; 21545 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell; Lives of the Leaders of Our Church Universal (3 vols.), 1879; 21544 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hill, A.E.; Miscellaneous Publications in Chemistry, 1904-1922; 21543 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Loomis, Elias; The Recent Progress of Astronomy, 1856; 21542 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Bessinger, Jess B. and Raymo, Robert R., eds.; Medieval Studies in Honor of Lillian Herlands Hornstein, 1976; 21541 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - The Tercentenary Announcements, 1609-1909: New York University Bulletin (2 copies), 21540 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227015 0
  - Shaw, Charles Gray; The Road to Culture, 1931; 21539 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell; Urgent Eastern Questions, 1913; 21538 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Stanton, Frank; Mass Media and Culture, 1947; 21537 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Turner, John Roscoe; The Ricardian Rent Theory in Early American Economics, 1921; 21536 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Millican, Charles Bowie; The First English Translation of the Prophecies of Merlin, 1931; 21535 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bond, R.P., Millican, C.B., Bowyer, J.W., and Smith, G.H.; A Collection of Chaucer Allusions, 1931; 21534 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ray, Gordon N.; Nineteenth Century English Fiction, 1964; 21533 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Sihler, E.G.; Three American Essays, 1902-1905; 21532 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - MacCracken, Henry Noble; The Family on Gramercy Park, 1949; 21531 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Shaw, Charles Gray; The Ground and Goal of Human Life, 1919; 21530 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Loomis, Elias; Treatise on Astronomy, 1865; 21529 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Wilkes, John W.; A Whig in Power, 1964; 21528 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Peel, Roy V.; The Political Clubs of New York City, 1935; 21527 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Sihler, E.G.; The Annals of Caesar, 1911; 21526 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Sihler, E.G.; Testimonium Animae, 1908; 21525 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Shaw, Charles Gray; The Value and Dignity of Human Life, 1911; 21524 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Shaw, Charles Gray; The Road to Happiness, 1937; 21523 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Hering, D.W.; Art in Clockmaking and Watchmaking, 1935; 21522 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Larkin, Oliver W.; Samuel F.B. Morse: An American Democratic Art, 1954; 21521 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Mitchell, Allan C.G. and Zemansky, Mark W.; Resonance Radiation and Excited Atoms, 1934; 21520 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Sihler, E.G.; Cicero of Arpinum, 1914; 21519 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Shaw, Charles Gray; The Ego and Its Place in the World, 1913; 21518 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Morse, Edward Lind, ed.; Samuel F.B. Morse: His Letters and Journals, 1914; 21517 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Vennard, John K.; Elementary Fluid Mechanics, 1940; 21516 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227016 8
  - Warren, Edward H.; Excerpts from Spartan Education, 1943; 21515 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Trager, Frank N., ed.; Behavior Science Bibliographies: Annotated Bibliography of Burma, 1956; 21514 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04227016 8
  - Smith, David Nichol, and McAdam, Edward L., eds.; The Poems of Samuel Johnson, 1941; 21513 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - McDonald, Philip B.; A Saga of the Seas, 1937; 21512 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Rollins, Hyder E.; A Gorgeous Gallery of Gallant Inventions, 1926; 21511 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Rusk, Howard A.; A World to Care For, 1972; 21510 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The Collected Works of Martin Andre Rosanoff, undated; 21509 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Rollins, Hyder Edward; The Pack of Autolycus, 1927; 21508 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Prentiss, G.L.; The Union Theological Seminary in the City of New York, 1899; 21507 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Saville, Thorndyke; New Horizons in Engineering Education, 1949; 21506 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Rosenblatt, Louise; Literature as Explanation, 1938; 21504 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The Tercentenary Announcements, 1609-1909: New York University Bulletin (3 copies), 21503 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Mergers and the Law, 1929; 21502 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Watkins, Myron W.; Oil: Stabilization or Conservation?, 1937; 21501 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Walsh, William F.; Outlines of the History of English and American Law, 1924; 21500 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Roe, Joseph Wickham; English and American Toolbuilders, 1916; 21499 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Gishford, Anthony, ed.; Tempo Quarterly (2 copies), 1951-1952; 21498 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Shotwell, James T., ed.; Government of Continental Europe, 1940; 21497 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Stahl, W.H.; The Systematic Handbook in Antiquity and the Early Middle Ages, 1964; 21496 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Stahl, William H.; "To A Better Understanding of Martianus Capella" (from Speculum), 1965; 21495 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Stahl, William H.; Ptolemese Geography, 1953; 21494 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Millican, Charles Bowie; Spenser and the Arthurian Legend, 1930; 21493 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Max, Louis William; The Time Relations of the Electrical and Mechanical Response of Heart Muscle, 1930; 21492 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227017 6
  - Stahl, William Harris; The Greek Heliocentric Theory and Its Abandonment, 1945; 21491 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Sihler, E.G.; From Augustus to Augustine (2 copies), 1923; 21490 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Sihler, Ernest G.; From Maumee to Thames and Tiber, 1930; 21489 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - McAdam, E.L.; "Dr. Johnson and Saunders Welch's Proposals" (from Review of English Studies), 1953; 21488 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - McAdam, E.L.; Dr. Johnson and the English Law, 1951; 21487 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - McAdam, E.L.; Samuel Johnson: Diaries, Prayers, and Annals, 1958; 21486 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - McAdam, E.L., and Milne, George; Johnson's Dictionary, 1963; 21485 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Federal Energy Administration: Project Independence, 1974; 21484 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Federal Energy Administration: Project Independence Report, 1974; 21483 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - McAdam, E.L.; "Wordsworth's Shipwreck" (from the PMLA), 1962; 21482 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - McAdam, E.L., ed.; The Yale Edition of the Works of Samuel Johnson, 1964; 21481 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - McConnell, John W.; The Evolution of Social Classes, 1942; 21480 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - McConnell, John W.; The Basic Teachings of the Great Economists, 1943; 21479 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - McAdam, E.L., and Milne, George, eds.; A Johnson Reader, 1964; 21478 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Rollins, Hyder E.; Cavalier and Puritan, 1923; 21477 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Rollins, Hyder E., ed.; Index to the Ballad Entries in the Stationers' Registers, 1924; 21476 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Rollins, Hyder E., ed.; A Handful of Pleasant Delights, 1924; 21475 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Park, Jacqueline; Charlie's Back in Town, 1975; 21474 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227858 3
  - Watkins, Myron W.; Industrial Combinations and Public Policy, 1927; 21473 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Nason, Arthur Huntington; Short Themes, 1909; 21472 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Zurcher, Arnold John; The Experiment with Democracy in Central Europe, 1933; 21471 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Watt, Homer Andrew; Bulletin of the University of Wisconsin, 1910; 21470 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - The Journal of English and Germanic Philology, 1929; 21469 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Wilkens, Frederick H.; The Source of Kleist's Review: Uber den Zustand der Schwartzen in Amerika, 1931; 21468 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Wood, Wallace; Catalog of Engravings, Etchings, and Aquatints, undated; 21467 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - McMahon, A. Philip; Preface to An American Philosophy of Art, 1945; 21466 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Draper, John W.; William Lyndon Wright: A Memoir (4 copies), 1923; 21465 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Wood, Wallace, ed.; The Hundred Greatest Men (books 3 and 4), 1885; 21464 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Mallery, Richard, ed.; Master Works of Travel and Exploration, 1948; 21463 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Wolfe, Don M.; Leveller Manifestoes of the Puritan Revolution, 1944; 21462 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rollins, Hyder E.; A Pepysian Garland, 1922; 21461 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Wendel, Hugo C.; The Evolution of Industrial Freedom in Prussia, 1921; 21460 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Lounsbury, Ralph Greenlee; The British Fishery at Newfoundland, 1634-1763, 1934; 21459 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Rollins, Hyder E., ed.; Old English Ballads, 1920; 21458 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Mallery, Richard D.; Our American Language, 1947; 21457 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Sihler, E.G.; A Lexicon to Caesar's Gallic War, 1891; 21456 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Rollins, Hyder E.; various articles, 1919-1923; 21455 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Watkins, Myron W.; various articles, 1928-1934; 21454 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Watkins, Myron W.; Business and the Law, 1934; 21453 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Watkins, Myron W.; Present Position and Prospects of Antitrust Policy, 1942; 21452 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Dworkin, Ronald, Miller, Karl, and Sennett, Richard, eds.; Humanities in Review, 1982; 21451 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227859 1
  - M'Ilvaine, Charles P.; The Evidences of Christianity, 1832; 21450 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Schlauch, Margaret, trans.; The Saga of the Volsungs, 1930; 21449 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Roelofs, H. Mark; The Language of Modern Politics, 1967; 21448 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Howe, M.A. deWolfe; James Ford Rhodes: American Historian, 1929; 21447 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Reid, James D.; The Telegraph in America, 1879; 21446 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Mason, Gregory; South of Yesterday, 1940; 21445 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Schlauch, Margaret; Chaucer's Constance and Accused Queens, 1927; 21444 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Melamid, Alexander; various articles, 1956-1959; 21443 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - various articles on English literature by Janet Spens and C. Bowie Millican, 1934-1938; 21442 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Schwartz, Bernard; Law and the Executive in Britain, 1949; 21441 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Schwarz, H. Stanley; Alexandre Dumas, fils: Dramatist, 1927; 21440 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Scott, Jonathan F.; War and Public Opinion, 1936; 21439 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Reither, Joseph, ed.; Master Works of History, 1948; 21438 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Rosenkampff, Arthur H.; Bookkeeping: Theory and Practice, 1924; 21437 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Davis, Pearce, and Meyer, Henry J., eds.; Labor Dispute Settlements in the Telephone Industry, 1942-1945, 1946; 21436 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Meyer, Adolf E.; The Development of Education in the Twentieth Century, 1949; 21435 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Zurcher, Arnold J.; Constitutions and Constitutional Trends Since World War II, 1951; 21434 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Sawhill, John C., Oshima, Keichi, and Maull, Hanns, W.; Energy: Managing the Transition, 1978; 21433 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Nuclear Power: Issues and Choices, 1977; 21432 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Nason, Arthur Huntington; Efficient Composition, 1917; 21431 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227860 9
  - Ford Foundation; Energy: The Next 20 Years, 1979; 21430 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Edward Conrad; The Borderland in the Civil War, 1927; 21429 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Smith, D. Nichol, and McAdam, E.L.; The Poems of Samuel Johnson, 1941; 21428 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Meyer, Adolf; Voltaire: Man of Justice, 1945; 21427 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Edward Conrad, and Zurcher, Arnold John, eds.; A Dictionary of American Politics, 1944; 21426 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Nason, John Huntington; James Shirley, Dramatist, 1915; 21425 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Sprague, Charles E.; Handbook of the Volapuk, 1888; 21424 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Horne, Herman Harrell, ed.; Quintilian on Education, undated; 21423 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Stahl, William H.; By Their Maps You Shall Know Them (from Archaeology), 1955; 21422 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Stahl, William Harris; "The Ancient Greek Astronomers" (from the Classical Journal), 1951; 21421 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Stack, Herbert J., Siebrecht, Elmer B., Elkow, J. Duke, eds.; Education for Safe Living, 1949; 21420 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Stein, Bruno; On Relief: The Economics of Poverty and Public Welfare, 1971; 21419 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Stahl, William; Macrobias: Commentary on the Dream of Scipio, 1952; 21418 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - South, Helen Pennock; The Proverbs of Alfred, 1931; 21417 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Homer W.; From Fish to Philosopher, 1953; 21416 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Smith, Edward Conrad; A Dictionary of American Politics, 1924; 21415 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Sinding, Paul C.; History of Scandinavia, 1858; 21414 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Newsom, Carroll V.; A University President Speaks Out: On Current Education, 1961; 21413 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Nock, Francis J.; An Introduction to Scientific German, 1937; 21412 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Taylor, W. C., A Manual of Ancient and Modern History, 1869; 245744 (Box 21, Item 1)
  - Wood, Wallace, The Hundred Greatest Men, 1892; 245747 (Box 21, Item 2)
  - Tappan, Henry P., The Elements of Logic, 1855; 245749 (Box 21, Item 3)
  - Tappan, Henry P., The Doctrine of the Will, 1840; 245752 (Box 21, Item 4)
  - Tappan, Henry P., Doctrine of the Will: Applied to Moral Agency and Responsibility, 1841; 245754 (Box 21, Item 5)
  - Loomis, Elias, Elements of Natural Philosophy, 1860; 245755 (Box 21, Item 6)
  - Loomis, Elias, The Elements of Astronomy, 1871; 245757 (Box 21, Item 7)
  - Loomis, Elias, Elements of Geometry, 1847; 245759 (Box 21, Item 8)
  - Loomis, Elias, Tables of Logarithms of Numbers, 1883; 245760 (Box 21, Item 9)
  - Lewis, Tayler, The Divine Human in the Scriptures, 1860; 245764 (Box 22, Item 1)
  - Hall, John, Eight Unto My Path, 1895; 245767 (Box 22, Item 2)
  - Loomis, Elias, A Treatise on Astronomy, 1892; 245768 (Box 22, Item 3)
  - Paine, Martin, Letters on the Cholera Asphyxia, 1832; 245771 (Box 22, Item 4)
  - Torrey, John, Compendium of the Flora of the Northern and Middle States, 1826; 245772 (Box 22, Item 5)
  - Loomis, Elias, The Elements of Arithmetic, 1863; 245773 (Box 22, Item 6)
  - Da Ponte, Lorenzo L. The Age and Rule of the Medici, 1833; 245774 (Box 22, Item 7)
  - Taylor, John S., A Review of Edwards' "Inquiry into the Freedom of Will", 1839; 245775 (Box 22, Item 8)
  - Loomis, Elias, The Elements of Algebra, 1874; 245776 (Box 22, Item 9)
  - Fuhrmann, Otto and Fritz Peters, "An Excerpt from Goethe's Faust", 1931; 245777 (Box 22, Item 10)
  - Patton, Robert P., "A Lecture on Classical and National Education", 1826; 245778 (Box 22, Item 11)
  - MacDougall, Robert, "University Training and the Doctoral Degree," reprinted from Education, 1904; 245779 (Box 22, Item 12)
  - Thiersch, Friedrich, Greek Tables on a Method of Teaching the Greek Paradigm, 1822; 245782 (Box 22, Item 13)
  - Mitchell-Vigneron, Jeannette, "Alexandre Liautard", 1982; 245783 (Box 22, Item 14)
  - Parker, Richard Alexander, "Claude de L'Estoille, Poet and Dramatist", 1930; 245784 (Box 22, Item 15)
  - Prince, J. Dyneley, "Some Passamaquoddy Witch Tales" and "On the Writing on the Wall at Belshazzar's Feast", 1868; 245785 (Box 22, Item 16)
  - Hackley, Charles W., A Treatise on Algebra, 1860; 245786 (Box 22, Item 17)
  - Loomis, Elias, Elements of Analytical Geometry and of the Differential and Integral Calculus, 1851; 245787 (Box 22, Item 18)
  - MacLay, An Address Delivered at a Public Meeting Held in Hope Street Baptist Church, Glasgow, 1840; 245788 (Box 22, Item 19)
  - Draper, John William, The Organization of Plants, 1844; 245789 (Box 23, Item 1)
  - Cousin, Victor, Elements of Psychology, 1856; 245790 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - Ellinwood, Mary G., Frank Field Ellinwood: His Life and Work, 1911; 245791 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - Guizot, M., General History of Civilization in Europe, 1846; 245792 (Box 23, Item 4)
  - Doyle, Martin (pseudonym of William Hickey), The Flower Garden, 1835; 245793 (Box 23, Item 5)
  - Henry, Caleb Sprague, A Household Liturgy, 1873; 245796 (Box 23, Item 6)
  - "Nothing to Wear: An Episode of City Life", 1857; 245797 (Box 23, Item 7)
  - Henry, C. S., Moral and Philosophical Essays, 1839; 245800 (Box 23, Item 8)
  - Lamb, Arthur B., "The Potential of Iron Calculated from Equilibria Measurements" and "An Equilibrium in the Cobaltammines", 1910-1911; 245801 (Box 23, Item 9)
  - Gerstenberg, Charles W., "Problems in Private Finance", 1916; 245808 (Box 23, Item 10)
  - Arnold, Rev. Thomas Kerchever, Cornelius Nepos, 1850 (Box 23)
  - Ermystead Grammar School, Skipton, 1877 (Box 23)
  - Noveck, Beth Simone, Smart Citizens, Smarter State, 2015 (Box 23)
  - Lempriere, J., Bilbiotheca Classica, 1832; 245809 (Box 24, Item 1)
  - Jordan, William George, Charles Waldo Haskins, 1923; 245810 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - Eddy, A. D., The Duties, Dangers, and Securities of Youth, 1836; 245811 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Torrey, John, Natural History of New York: Botany (volume I), 1843; 245812 (Box 24, Item 4)
  - Torrey, John, Natural History of New York: Botany (volume II), 1843; 245824 (Box 24, Item 5)
  - Draper, John W., A Treatise on the Forces Which Produce the Organization of Plants, 1844; 245826 (Box 24, Item 6)
  - Edmonson, Thomas William, "Documents Extracted from the Public Record Office Concerning Skipton-in-Craven, Yorkshire", undated; 245827 (Box 24, Item 7)
  - Wertenbaker, Thomas Jefferson, The Old South: The Founding of American Civilization, 1942; 247171 (Box 25, Item 1)
  - Morse, Samuel F.B., Foreign Conspiracy Against the Liberties of the United States, 1855; 247172 (Box 25, Item 2)
  - Vail, Alfred, The American Electro Magnetic Telegraph, 1845; 247173 (Box 25, Item 3)
  - McLouth, Lawrence A., Verses, 1910; 247174 (Box 25, Item 4)
  - Mathews, J.M., Recollections of Persons and Events, Chiefly in the City of New York: Being Selections From His Journal, 1865; 247175 (Box 25, Item 5)
  - Mathews, J.M., Recollections of Persons and Events, Chiefly in the City of New York: Being Selections From His Journal (copy 2), 1865; 247179 (Box 25, Item 6)
  - Stansbury, Howard, Expedition Maps of the Great Salt lake and Fort Leavenworth, 1850; 247176 (Box 25, Item 7)
  - Mathews, J.M., The Bible and Men of Learning, 1855; 247177 (Box 25, Item 8)
  - Mathews, J.M., The Bible and Civil Government, 1851; 247178 (Box 25, Item 9)
  - Mitchell, Allan C.G. and Zemansky, Mark W., Resonance Radiation and Excited Atoms, 1934; 247180 (Box 25, Item 10)
  - Prime, Samuel Irenæus, The Life of Samuel F.B. Morse, 1875; 247181 (Box 25, Item 11)
  - Prime, Samuel Irenæus, The Life of Samuel F.B. Morse (copy 2), 1875; 247182 (Box 25, Item 12)
  - Russell, Isaac Franklin, Outline Study of Law, 1894; 247183 (Box 25, Item 13)
  - McIlvaine, Charles P., "Collection of Lectures", Probably 1850s; 247184 (Box 25, Item 14)
  - Monaghan, French Travellers in the United States 1765-1932 (A Bibliography), 1933; 247185 (Box 25, Item 15)
  - Sihler, Ernest G., C. Iulius Caesar, 1912; 247186 (Box 25, Item 16)
  - Paine, Martyn, A Review of Theoretical Geology, 1856; 247187 (Box 25, Item 17)
  - Russell, Isaac Franklin, Lectures on Law for Women, 1893; 247188 (Box 25, Item 18)
  - Nordheimer, Isaac, A Critical Grammar of the Hebrew Language, 1838; 247189 (Box 25, Item 19)